Contact

lindseycarter5188@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lindsey-carter-57538520 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Healthcare CCRN

Lindsey Carter

RN, BSN, CCRN

Greater Seattle Area

Summary

Dedicated and compassionate registered nurse with over seven years of experience in a fast paced critical care setting. Possesses an exceptional work ethic, strong interpersonal communication skills, and the ability to learn quickly and adapt to new and challenging environments. Advanced to Charge RN role in 2013, which has further refined leadership and management skills.

Experience

CHI Franciscan Health
PACU Registered Nurse
July 2018 - Present (2 years)
Federal Way

Capital Medical Center
Emergency Department Registered Nurse
January 2018 - July 2018 (7 months)
Olympia, WA

MultiCare Health System 7 years 4 months

ICU Registered Nurse | Charge Nurse May 2015 - December 2017 (2 years 8 months) Puyallup, WA

- * Staff and charge RN in a 14 bed ICU caring for patients over the age of 18.
- * Charge RN role approximately 50% of shifts. Manage about 10 staff members per shift.
- * Provide high quality primary care for patients in a 1:2 or 1:1 ratio.
- * Patient population includes respiratory failure, sepsis, ARDS, GI bleed, postop, stroke, TPA (CVA, PE), EKOS (PE, DVT), shock (septic, cardiogenic, hemorrhagic, anaphylactic), IABP, DKA, renal failure, dialysis (HD, CRRT), ETOH withdrawal, overdose, organ donation

Critical Care Center Registered Nurse | Charge Nurse

April 2011 - May 2015 (4 years 2 months)

Puyallup, WA

- * Staff RN in a 40 bed combined ICU/PCU caring for patients over the age of 18.
- * Cross-trained to care for ICU level patients in June 2012.
- * Advanced to Charge RN position in August 2013.
- * Charge RN role approximately 50% of shifts. Managed about 26 staff members per shift.

PCU Registered Nurse September 2010 - April 2011 (8 months) Puyallup, WA

* Staff RN in a 24 bed PCU caring for patients over the age of 18.

Education

University of Portland
Bachelor of Science - BS, Nursing · (2006 - 2010)